classscout.com 2011-12-31

# ClassScout

### YOUR PRIVACY IS OUR MAJOR CONCERN. 

The following policy details how we gather information, how that information is shared, and what practices ClassScout.com implements to ensure your information is safe and protected. 

Use of the site indicates agreement with the Privacy Policy. 

### What information does ClassScout.com gather? 

ClassScout.com gathers information in order to bring business-to-business services to consumers, free of charge. ClassScout.com considers business-specific information to include contact names, addresses, phone/fax numbers, e-mail/website addresses, and credit card numbers. Additionally, we create vendor profiles that may contain proprietary information. 

### Use of Information:

ClassScout.com gathers information in an attempt to introduce business-to-business vendors to consumers in order to satisfy their professional needs. 

Registration: 

Registration to obtain general information is not required; however vendors and those seeking vendor services are required to register on www.ClassScout.com 

While visiting www.ClassScout.com individuals can view pages and need not worry about revealing personal information. ClassScout.com collects information via industry standard web log files that include a URL address, where you presently are located, browser information and IP address. ClassScout.com may also use “cookies.” 

ClassScout.com is the sole owner of the information collected on ClassScout.com. ClassScout.com collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site. 

Cookies: 

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record keeping

purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. 

We use persistent cookies.  A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file. 

Cookies are stored only if you select to save your password on the login screen.  A cookie is created so that we are able to retrieve your settings. We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don't have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. 

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited. 

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. 

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by www.ClassScout.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. You may disable cookies if your browser permits. Please be advised that this may prevent you from accessing certain features of ClassScout.com. Having trouble while cookies is disabled? Call our Customer Service department at 1-866.905.3637. 

Log Files: 

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files.  This information includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. 

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 

We do not link this automatically collected data to personally identifiable information. 

We use a third-party tracking service through Google and Overture that uses cookies [log files] to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site. 

Links to other sites: 

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled 

by ClassScout.com. Please be aware that ClassScout.com, is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. 

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. 

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site. 

Security: 

The security of your personal information is important to us.  When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.  No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.  Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at custserv@ClassScout.com 

Information on circulation: 

Once signed up with ClassScout.com, you may receive additional publications such as newsletters and e-mails that contain content regarding the website, content changes and special promotions. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. Please see, “Choice and Opt-Out 

Ordering services:

In order for ClassScout.com to service you properly, you will need to provide us with company-specific information. Both vendors and those submitting requests are required to complete an online form which requests specific data. This includes contact information, demographics and information designed to assist you with searching for specific vendor/request-related inquiries. Various departments at ClassScout.com may review your company's information. Credit card information is stored securely through encryption and SSL connection. We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. 

Surveys & Contests : 

Occasionally and in order to heighten your experience with ClassScout.com, we may ask you to complete a survey, or suggest you enter a contest. Any information obtained via a survey or contest is held in the strictest of confidence. Information regarding contest winners may be communicated through a corporate news publication, however each contest will display a disclaimer saying so. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary, and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. 

Information sharing policy- Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable): 

We share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our customers. This information does not identify individual users. ClassScout.com will refer business related information in leads to interested parties. ClassScout.com never sells or releases company information to other parties unless it is directly related to a sales lead. 

### Agents: 

We use an outside credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. This company does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes. 

Access – changing information: 

Vendors with ClassScout.com can change profile information at any time by accessing their profiles with the appropriate sign-in name and password. Individuals who place requests can update, change or remove information by contacting custserv@ClassScout.com . 

Service Providers: 

ClassScout.com is considered a “third-party referral service.” We use other third parties [or vendors] to provide business related services on our site. When you sign up to ClassScout.com we will share business related (non-proprietary) information as necessary for the third party to provide that service. 

Choice/Opt Out:

Receiving additional information such as newsletters, updates and other publications is strictly voluntary. 

We provide you the opportunity to ‘opt-out' of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our order form. 

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by e-mailing us at custserv@ClassScout.com . 

Legal disclaimer: 

ClassScout.com reserves the right to disclose identifiable information as required by law, and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and to comply with judicial proceedings, court order or legal processes served on website. 

Business Transitions: 

In the event ClassScout.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via a prominent notice on our website for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. 

Changes in privacy statement: 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you her, by a notice on our homepage.
